<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 10:49:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things I should know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 10:49:27 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-know/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a semester it has been so far. It&amp;rsquo;s very busy, but I am thoroughly enjoying myself and my new life here in Chicago. With that being said: I&amp;rsquo;ve still got to do more.&#xA;We met with Benson a couple days ago, and the expectation is that we will move through this mapping class group material very quickly. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to backfill some of the main proofs&#xA;which are glossed over in the book, but this takes time, and I&amp;rsquo;m not going fast enough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 10:31:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think that the main mistake I made with my previous &amp;ldquo;math blog&amp;rdquo; is that I miscalculated my desire to write long, drawn out mathematical arguments in the context of a blog post,&#xA;when such things would be much better suited for a set of lecture notes. A blog should probably be a bit more whimsical, concise, and conversational: that is what I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to achieve here.&#xA;I probably won&amp;rsquo;t even talk exclusively about math, although I am a (baby) graduate student in mathematics at UChicago, so alas, mathematics more or less dominates my life. Having said that, this&#xA;will be a forum for shorter, perhaps even incomplete thoughts, my general thoughts and experiences pursuing a PhD in mathematics, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure much more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
